canarahsbclife.com 2010-05-18

# Canara HSBC Life Insurance - Privacy Policy

### Canara HSBC Oriental Bank of Commerce Life Insurance Company Limited Privacy Principles

Our business has been built on trust between our customers and ourselves. To preserve the confidentiality of all information you provide to us, we maintain the following privacy principles:

  * We only collect personal information that we believe to be relevant and required to understand your financial needs and to conduct our business. 

  * We use your personal information to provide you with better customer services and products.

  * We may pass your personal information to our Sales staff or agents, as permitted by law

  * We will not disclose your personal information to any external organisation unless we have your consent or are required by law or have previously informed you.

  * We may be required from time to time to disclose your personal information to Governmental or judicial bodies or agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.

  * We aim to keep your personal information on our records accurate and up-to-date. 

  * We maintain strict security systems designed to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information by anyone, including our staff.

  * All our staff and all third parties with permitted access to your information are specifically required to observe our confidentiality obligations.

By maintaining our commitment to these principles, we at Canara HSBC Oriental Bank of Commerce Life Insurance Company Limited will ensure that we respect the inherent trust that you place in us.

### Your privacy matters to us

This section provides specific details of how we treat any personal information you might wish to provide us when you visit this site.

Data Security

  * Security is our top priority. Canara HSBC Oriental Bank of Commerce Life Insurance Company Limited (hereinafter referred to as "The Company") will strive at all times to ensure that your personal data will be protected against unauthorised or accidental access, processing or erasure. We maintain this commitment to data security by implementing appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to safeguard and secure your personal data. 

Collection of Personal Information

  * Use of "cookies" Your visit to this site may be recorded for analysis on the number of visitors to the site and general usage patterns. Some of this information will be gathered through the use of "cookies". Cookies are small bits of information that are automatically stored on a person's web browser in their computer that can be retrieved by this site. Should you wish to disable these cookies you may do so by changing the setting on your browser.

  * Marketing Promotions : Occasionally we may collect personal information from visitors to this site and those individuals that participate in a contest or promotion (online or over the telephone,or at one of our branches). Such information is only collected from individuals who voluntarily provide us with their personal information. We may use this information to advise them of products, services and other marketing materials, which we think, may be of interest to them. We may also invite visitors to this site to participate in market research and surveys and other similar activities

If we do ask you to provide personal information, we will always specify the purpose for which such personal information is collected and ensure that it is only used for the purpose specified at the time of collection.

**IMPORTANT:  **By accessing this web site and any of its pages you are agreeing to the terms set out above. Thank you for choosing Canara HSBC Oriental Bank of Commerce Life Insurance Company Limited.
